https://www.biorelief.com/privacy-policy-for-biorelief-com

Skip to contentPrivacy Policy StatementWe never rent or sell our customers’ data to anyone. All information held is strictly confidential.This is the web site of BioRelief.com.Our postal address is: 6250 NW 27th Way Fort Lauderdale, FL 33309For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.With respect to cookies: We set one cookie to help our log analysis program accurately reflect user sessions. We use Urchin’s UTM for our log analyis. No personal information is contained within this cookie.We do not normally send promotional e-mail to our customers. We have an opt in list for our newsletter and only send promotional mail to those who have opted in. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above e-mail address.If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.We do not normally share your information with any outside organizations. We have no agreements to share this information and can not imagine a situation where we would begin sharing this with anyone outside this organization.With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We do, however, advertise on Google’s adwords and Overture. Both of these companies may set a cookie on your computer when you click on one of our ads. This allows us to determine if the ad is effective or not.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.Upon reasonable request we can provide site visitors with access to information that we have collected and that we maintain about them. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number. AllBrandsCamping & TravelCamping & TravelCathetersConditionsExternal CathetersFree ShippingPersonal HygienePortable ToiletsPortable ToiletsPortable UrinalRestroom AccessoriesRestroom AccessoriesSenior Home CareSpecial NeedsSupplementsUncategorized Search for:
HomeIncontinenceAdult UnderwearBedwettingExternal CathetersIncontinence ProductsUrologyCathetersExternal CathetersIntermittent CathetersPersonal HygienePersonal Hygiene ProductsPortable ToiletsOdor ManagementSpecial Needs CareBidetsBidetsPortable BidetsToilet Seat BidetsCamp & TravelCamping & Travel HygieneCamping & Travel ToiletsCamping ShowersFirst AidPortable BidetsPortable ToiletsTailgating SuppliesSenior CareBack PainNerve PainReduced MobilityRestroom AccessoriesSupport HardwareSenior Home CareSupplementsBrandsAttends HealthcareBioBidetBioReliefCleanisColoplastGoBidetPotty MDPrefenseRebuilder MedicalTenaTotoTravel JohnMy AccountRecent OrdersAccount DetailsPassword ResetBlog
Login
Login Username or email address *
Password *
Remember me
Log in Lost your password?Register Email address *
Password * Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website and to manage access to your account. More details in our privacy policy.
Register
